{
    "subject": "resource/The_Mating_Call",
    "predicate": "property/language",
    "object": "English intertitles",
    "human_readable": "The Mating Call has English intertitles.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.884051501750946,
            "question": "What language are the intertitles in 'The Mating Call'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5362217426300049,
            "question": "Besides English, what other languages might have been used for intertitles in this film?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.33351796865463257,
            "question": "What does the term 'intertitles' refer to in filmmaking?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.28887516260147095,
            "question": "Can you give examples of films that use intertitles?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.2695979177951813,
            "question": "Are there any famous directors known for using intertitles in their films?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.23408488929271698,
            "question": "What is the purpose of intertitles in a film?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.22684063017368317,
            "question": "Why might a film utilize intertitles in its storytelling?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.20853517949581146,
            "question": "What is the historical context surrounding the use of intertitles in film?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.1695650815963745,
            "question": "How do intertitles contribute to the viewer's understanding of a film?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.1607675999403,
            "question": "Is 'The Mating Call' a silent film?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The Mating Call has English intertitles.",
            "html": "dbpedia_4684_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=How do intertitles contribute to the viewer's understanding of a film?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4684_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the historical context surrounding the use of intertitles in film?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4684_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Why might a film utilize intertitles in its storytelling?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4684_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4684_103.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4684_113.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4684_25.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4684_34.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4684_35.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4684_54.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4684_77.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4684_81.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4684_9.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4684_95.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'} \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the answer in the requested format:\n\n```\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThis is because the document mentions that \"The Mating Call\" is a silent film with \"English intertitles\"."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents mention that \"The Mating Call\" is a silent film with English intertitles, which supports the statement that \"The Mating Call has English intertitles.\""
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}